tp-link.com.au 2007-09-13

# Anyware Computer Accessories

| | 

|  |   Search  |     |  |     |   
---|---|---|---|---  
  
Home > Footer Links > Privacy Policy  
  
Terms & Conditions

Anyware recognises that your privacy is imperative to you and that you have a right to control your personal information. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that seriously. Unless you give us explicit consent to act otherwise, Anyware is committed to protecting and maintaining the privacy, accuracy and security of your personal information. 

Anyware collects personal information for the following purposes :

  * selling, promoting and provision of goods and services

  * maintenance of product warranties

  * provision of information on our products and services that you request via post, telephone or email

If you do not wish to provide Anyware with personal details, then we will not be able to provide you with the products, services and warranty that you require. Anyware may disclose your personal information to organizations within Australia to facilitate us in providing some products and services. These organizations have compliant privacy procedures in place and must not use your personal information for any other purposes. You have control over how your personal information is used. Should you no longer wish to receive any particular materials, correct and update any personal information or have any question about this Privacy Policy, please contact by email [ privacy@anyware.com.au](mailto:privacy@anyware.com.au)
